A Guide to the the Student Council Office Administrative Files, 1972-1995
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Gay and Lesbian Concerns
  - Student Council Survey on Sexuality 1989, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Virginia Advocate 1987 (Box 33)
- Restricted Files
  - Bad Checks (Restricted) 1984-1985 (Box 34)
  - Beverly Investigation (Restricted) 1983 (Box 34)
  - Escort Service Accident (Restricted) 1984 (Box 34)
  - Escort Service Payroll (Restricted) 1989-1990 (Box 34)
  - Insurance (Restricted) 1981-1986 (Box 34)